{
    "id": "9edcac643d8e44d3bb68c1fffdb3913a",
    "title": "Used to",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d0cb0b3763d342faa2900bdbbc8f8d42",
            "title": "Used To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I am not used to ………………….. in cold climates.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "live",
                        "living",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When we were kids, we …………………. go swimming in the evenings.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "were used to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She used to …………………. a lot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "write",
                        "writing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am not used to ………………….. on the left.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "drive",
                        "driving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn’t use to ………………….. fish or meat, but now I do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "eat",
                        "eating"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He quit his job in Saudi Arabia because he ………………… .. living in such a hot country.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was not used to",
                        "did not used to",
                        "did not use to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are used to ………………….. in poverty.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "live",
                        "living"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You will soon get used to ………………….. things on your own.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "doing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "First-time mothers often find it difficult to get used to ………………….. up in the middle of the night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… to like him, but now I do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used not",
                        "didn't use",
                        "use to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}